Guide to The Parasite Archive MSS.333
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series V: Audio recordings
  - "Parasite Day 2, Tape #1", July 5, 1998; ID: 333.0024 (Box 6, Media ID: 333.0024)
  - "Parasite, Tape 2, Day 2", 1998; ID: 333.0025 (Box 6, Media ID: 333.0025)
  - "Le (Dernder) Tape", July 4, 1998; ID: 333.0026 (Box 6, Media ID: 333.0026)
  - "Parasite Discussion Tape #1", July 28, 1998; ID: 333.0027 (Box 6, Media ID: 333.0027)
  - "Publication Meeting", October 8, 1998; ID: 333.0028 (Box 6, Media ID: 333.0028, Case 333.0028)
- Series VI: Data Storage
  Subseries VI: Data Storage consists of computer files on disk.
  Born-digital materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  - "Parasite News Data", 5/28/98; ID: 333.3.0001 (Box 6, Media ID: 333.3.0001)
    Format: HD 3.5" Disk
    Capacity: [unknown]
- OVERSIZE Series I: Parasite Document Collection
  Series I: Parasite Document Collection preserves a collection of contemporary and historical documents relating to project-based activity. Materials on particular artists and works include documentation of completed projects and, where possible, proposals, contracts, correspondence, and ephemera. These materials are arranged alphabetically by artist, item title, or subject.
  - REPO History Collective [2 of 2], 1993 - 1996 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Shedhalle Zurich [2 of 3], 1994 - 1997 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Shedhalle Zurich [3 of 3], 1994 (Folder 17)
- OVERSIZE Series II: Services: A Working-Group Exhibition
  - Dion, Mark: "Sculpture Chicago" [2 of 2], 1992 - 1993 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Group Material: Subculture [Flyer], 1983 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Sonsbeek '93: International Art Exhibition, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 5)